Sentence #,Word,Tag
Sentence: 1," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 1,rejects ,O
Sentence: 1," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 1,call to boycott ,O
Sentence: 1," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 1,lamb ,O
Sentence: 2,Peter ,O
Sentence: 2," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 2," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 2,1996-08-22 The ,O
Sentence: 2," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 2,said on Thursday it disagreed with ,O
Sentence: 2," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 2,advice to consumers to shun ,O
Sentence: 2," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 3,Germany 's representative to the ,O
Sentence: 3," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 3,'s veterinary committee ,O
Sentence: 3," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 3," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 3,until the scientific advice was clearer ,O
Sentence: 4," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 4,'s chief spokesman ,O
Sentence: 4," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 4,told a news briefing ,O
Sentence: 5," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 6," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 6,said a proposal last month by ,O
Sentence: 6," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 6,Farm Commissioner ,O
Sentence: 6," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 7,Fischler proposed ,O
Sentence: 7," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 7,measures after reports from ,O
Sentence: 7," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 7,and ,O
Sentence: 7," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 7,that under laboratory conditions sheep could contract ,O
Sentence: 7," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 7,( ,O
Sentence: 7," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 7,) -- mad cow disease ,O
Sentence: 8,But ,O
Sentence: 8," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 8,agreed to review his proposal after the ,O
Sentence: 8," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 9,Spanish Farm Minister ,O
Sentence: 9," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 9,had earlier accused ,O
Sentence: 9," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 9,at an ,O
Sentence: 9," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 10,Only ,O
Sentence: 10," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 10,and ,O
Sentence: 10," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 10,backed ,O
Sentence: 10," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 10,'s proposal ,O
Sentence: 11,The ,O
Sentence: 11," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 13," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 13,government advice to consumers to avoid ,O
Sentence: 13," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 13,lamb might influence consumers across ,O
Sentence: 13," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 14," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 14," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 14,"'s lead , ",O
Sentence: 14," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 14,( ,O
Sentence: 14," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 14,) chairman ,O
Sentence: 14," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 14,said on ,O
Sentence: 14," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 15," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 16,"Germany imported 47,600 sheep from ",O
Sentence: 16," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 16,"last year , nearly half of total imports ",O
Sentence: 17,"It brought in 4,275 tonnes of ",O
Sentence: 17," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 17,"mutton , some 10 percent of overall imports ",O
Sentence: 18,-DOCSTART- Rare ,O
Sentence: 18," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 18,"song draft sells for almost $ 17,000 ",O
Sentence: 20,A ,O
Sentence: 20," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 20,"restaurant paid 10,925 pounds ( $ 16,935 ) for the draft of ",O
Sentence: 20," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 20,", which ",O
Sentence: 20," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 20,penned on a piece of ,O
Sentence: 20," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 20,hotel stationery in late 1966 ,O
Sentence: 21,At the end of a January 1967 concert in the ,O
Sentence: 21," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 21,city of ,O
Sentence: 21," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 22," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 22,'s former girlfriend ,O
Sentence: 22," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 22,", who lived with him from 1966 to 1969 ",O
Sentence: 23," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 23,"to store his drugs , which an anonymous ",O
Sentence: 23," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 23,"purchaser bought for 5,060 pounds ( $ 7,845 ) ",O
Sentence: 24,The guitarist died of a drugs overdose in 1970 aged 27 ,O
Sentence: 25,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 25," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 25,says ,O
Sentence: 25," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 25,spoils atmosphere for talks ,O
Sentence: 26,BEIJING 1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 26," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 26,on Thursday accused ,O
Sentence: 26," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 26," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 26,with a visit to ,O
Sentence: 26," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 26,by ,O
Sentence: 26," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 26,Vice President ,O
Sentence: 26," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 26,this week that infuriated ,O
Sentence: 26," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 27," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 27,only hours after ,O
Sentence: 27," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 27," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 27,", ",O
Sentence: 27," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 27,spokesman ,O
Sentence: 27," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 27,told ,O
Sentence: 27," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 27," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 27,authorities ,O
Sentence: 28,State media quoted ,O
Sentence: 28," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 28,'s top negotiator with ,O
Sentence: 28," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 28,", ",O
Sentence: 28," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 28,", as telling a visiting group from ",O
Sentence: 28," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 29," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 29,quoted ,O
Sentence: 29," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 29,as saying ,O
Sentence: 30,The foreign ministry 's ,O
Sentence: 30," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 30,told ,O
Sentence: 30," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 30,in an interview he had read reports of ,O
Sentence: 30," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 30," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 30,", which ",O
Sentence: 30," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 30,considers a renegade province ,O
Sentence: 31,"China , which has long opposed all ",O
Sentence: 31," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 31," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 31,this week by ,O
Sentence: 31," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 31,Vice President ,O
Sentence: 31," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 32," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 32," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 32,says time right for ,O
Sentence: 32," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 32,talks ,O
Sentence: 33,BEIJING 1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 33," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 33,has said it was time for political talks with ,O
Sentence: 33," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 34," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 34,news agency quoted ,O
Sentence: 34," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 34,", executive vice chairman of the ",O
Sentence: 34," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 34,", as saying late on Wednesday ",O
Sentence: 35,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 35," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 35,July car registrations up 14.2 pct yr / yr ,O
Sentence: 36,FRANKFURT 1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 36," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 43,Opel ,O
Sentence: 43," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 43,together with ,O
Sentence: 43," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 44,Third was ,O
Sentence: 44," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 44,"with 35,563 registrations , or 11.7 percent ",O
Sentence: 45,Only ,O
Sentence: 45," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 45,and ,O
Sentence: 45," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 47,Porsche 's registrations fell to 554 from 643 ,O
Sentence: 48,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 48," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 48,SOCIALISTS GIVE GREEN LIGHT TO PM FOR ELECTIONS ,O
Sentence: 49,ATHENS 1996-08-22 The ,O
Sentence: 49," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 49," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 49,"to call snap elections , its general secretary ",O
Sentence: 49," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 49,told reporters ,O
Sentence: 50,Prime Minister ,O
Sentence: 50," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 50," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 51," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 51,", ",O
Sentence: 51," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 51,+301 3311812-4 -DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 51," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 51,sets ,O
Sentence: 51," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 51,100 million six-year bond ,O
Sentence: 52," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 53," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 53," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 53,AMT ,O
Sentence: 53," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 53," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 53,= DENOMS ( K ) 1-10-100 SALE LIMITS ,O
Sentence: 53," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 53,/ ,O
Sentence: 53," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 53,/ ,O
Sentence: 53," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 53,NEG PLG NO CRS DEFLT NO FORCE MAJ = GOV LAW ,O
Sentence: 53," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 53," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 53,IS JOINT LEAD MANAGER -- ,O
Sentence: 53," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 53,+44 171 542 7658 -DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 53," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 53,sets $ 300 million January 1999 FRN ,O
Sentence: 54," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 55," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 55,( ,O
Sentence: 55," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 55," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 55,DENOMS ( K ) 1-10-100 SALE LIMITS ,O
Sentence: 55," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 55,/ ,O
Sentence: 55," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 55,/ ,O
Sentence: 55," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 55,/ ,O
Sentence: 55," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 55," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 55,+44 171 542 8863 -DOCSTART- Port conditions update - ,O
Sentence: 55," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 55,- ,O
Sentence: 55," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 56," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 56,conditions from ,O
Sentence: 56," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 56,-- ,O
Sentence: 56," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 56,", Aug 10 - waiting time at ",O
Sentence: 56," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 56,and ,O
Sentence: 56," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 56,presently 24 hours ,O
Sentence: 57,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 57," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 57,plays down fears of war with ,O
Sentence: 57," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 58," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 58," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 58," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 58,1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 58," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 58,'s outgoing peace negotiator with ,O
Sentence: 58," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 59,Itamar ,O
Sentence: 59," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 59,", who as ",O
Sentence: 59," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 59,'s ambassador to ,O
Sentence: 59," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 59,conducted unfruitful negotiations with ,O
Sentence: 59," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 59,", told ",O
Sentence: 59," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 59,it looked like ,O
Sentence: 59," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 59,wanted to talk rather than fight ,O
Sentence: 60,It appears to me the ,O
Sentence: 60," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 60,priority is still to negotiate ,O
Sentence: 61,The ,O
Sentence: 61," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 61," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 61,"is that this is essentially a storm in a teacup , he said ",O
Sentence: 63,He will be replaced by ,O
Sentence: 63," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 63,", a former ",O
Sentence: 63," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 63,envoy to ,O
Sentence: 63," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 63,and right-wing ,O
Sentence: 63," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 63,party politician ,O
Sentence: 64,Israel on Wednesday sent ,O
Sentence: 64," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 64,"a message , via ",O
Sentence: 64," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 66," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 66,television reported that ,O
Sentence: 66," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 66,had recently test fired a missile ,O
Sentence: 68,The message that we sent to ( ,O
Sentence: 68," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 68,President ,O
Sentence: 68," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 68,) ,O
Sentence: 68," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 68,is that ,O
Sentence: 68," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 68," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 68,Foreign Minister ,O
Sentence: 68," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 68,told ,O
Sentence: 68," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 68,in an interview ,O
Sentence: 69,Tension has mounted since ,O
Sentence: 69," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 69,Prime Minister ,O
Sentence: 69," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 69,took office in June vowing to retain the ,O
Sentence: 69," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 69,captured from ,O
Sentence: 69," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 69,in the 1967 ,O
Sentence: 69," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 69,war ,O
Sentence: 73," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 73,said ,O
Sentence: 74,We expect from ,O
Sentence: 74," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 74,", if its face is to peace , that it will answer ",O
Sentence: 74," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 75,"We do not want a war , ",O
Sentence: 75," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 75,forbid ,O
Sentence: 76,No one benefits from wars ,O
Sentence: 77,Israel 's ,O
Sentence: 77," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 77,television said ,O
Sentence: 77," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 77,had sent a calming signal to ,O
Sentence: 77," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 78," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 78,gave no source for the report ,O
Sentence: 79,Netanyahu and ,O
Sentence: 79," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 80,The television also said that ,O
Sentence: 80," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 80,had sent messages to reassure ,O
Sentence: 80," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 80,via ,O
Sentence: 80," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 80,", the ",O
Sentence: 80," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 80,and ,O
Sentence: 80," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 81," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 81," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 81,diplomat denies nurses stranded in ,O
Sentence: 81," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 82," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 82,1996-08-22 A ,O
Sentence: 82," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 82,diplomat on Thursday denied a ,O
Sentence: 82," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 82,tabloid report this week that ,O
Sentence: 82," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 82,was refusing exit visas to 100 ,O
Sentence: 82," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 84," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 84,embassy 's charge d'affaires in ,O
Sentence: 84," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 84,", ",O
Sentence: 84," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 84,", told ",O
Sentence: 84," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 84,by telephone ,O
Sentence: 86,He said that there are an estimated 800 ,O
Sentence: 86," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 86,nurses working in ,O
Sentence: 86," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 87," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 87,Two ,O
Sentence: 87," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 87,opposition leaders meet in ,O
Sentence: 87," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 88," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 88," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 88," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 88,1996-08-22 An ,O
Sentence: 88," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 88,exile group based in ,O
Sentence: 88," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 88,vowed on Thursday to extend support to ,O
Sentence: 88," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 88,'s ,O
Sentence: 88," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 88,rebels after they were attacked by ,O
Sentence: 88," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 88,troops deep inside ,O
Sentence: 88," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 88,last month ,O
Sentence: 89,A ,O
Sentence: 89," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 89,statement said its leader ,O
Sentence: 89," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 89,met in ,O
Sentence: 89," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 89,the Secretary-General of the ,O
Sentence: 89," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 89,( ,O
Sentence: 89," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 89,) ,O
Sentence: 89," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 89,on Wednesday and voiced his support to ,O
Sentence: 89," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 89,'s rebel ,O
Sentence: 89," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 90," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 90,emphasised that the ,O
Sentence: 90," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 90," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 91," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 91,and the ,O
Sentence: 91," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 91,oppositions ,O
Sentence: 92,Iran heavily bombarded targets in northern ,O
Sentence: 92," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 92,in July in pursuit of ,O
Sentence: 92," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 92,guerrillas based in ,O
Sentence: 92," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 92,areas outside the control of the government in ,O
Sentence: 92," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 93," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 93," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 93,areas bordering ,O
Sentence: 93," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 93," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 93,( ,O
Sentence: 93," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 93,) group ,O
Sentence: 94,PUK and ,O
Sentence: 94," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 94,'s ,O
Sentence: 94," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 94,( ,O
Sentence: 94," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 94,) the two main ,O
Sentence: 94," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 94,"factions , have had northern ",O
Sentence: 94," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 94,under their control since ,O
Sentence: 94," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 94,forces were ousted from ,O
Sentence: 94," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 94,in the 1991 ,O
Sentence: 94," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 95," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 95," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 95,ceasefire last year ,O
Sentence: 96,Mujahideen ,O
Sentence: 96," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 96,said ,O
Sentence: 96," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 96,troops had also been shelling ,O
Sentence: 96," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 96,positions in ,O
Sentence: 96," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 96,region in ,O
Sentence: 96," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 96,province near the ,O
Sentence: 96," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 96,border over the last two days ,O
Sentence: 97,It said about 100 ,O
Sentence: 97," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 97,were killed or wounded in the attack ,O
Sentence: 98,Both ,O
Sentence: 98," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 98,and ,O
Sentence: 98," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 98," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 98,in pursuit of their own ,O
Sentence: 98," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 98,rebels ,O
Sentence: 99,A ,O
Sentence: 99," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 99,air force in southern ,O
Sentence: 99," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 99,protects ,O
Sentence: 99," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 99,from possible attacks by ,O
Sentence: 99," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 99,troops ,O
Sentence: 100,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 100," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 100,riyal rates steady in quiet summer trade ,O
Sentence: 101,MANAMA 1996-08-22 The spot ,O
Sentence: 101," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 104,The spot riyal was put at 3.7504 / 06 to the dollar ,O
Sentence: 106,"One-year funds were at six , 5-7/8 percent ",O
Sentence: 107,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 107," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 107,approves ,O
Sentence: 107," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 107,'s flight to ,O
Sentence: 107," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 108," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 108,1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 108," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 108,gave ,O
Sentence: 108," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 108,President ,O
Sentence: 108," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 108," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 108,", ending a brief ",O
Sentence: 108," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 108,"crisis , an ",O
Sentence: 108," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 108,adviser said ,O
Sentence: 109,The problem is over ,O
Sentence: 110," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 110,"before Monday , ",O
Sentence: 110," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 110,told ,O
Sentence: 110," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 111," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 111,had been scheduled to meet former ,O
Sentence: 111," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 111,prime minister ,O
Sentence: 111," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 111,in the ,O
Sentence: 111," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 111,town of ,O
Sentence: 111," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 111,on Thursday but the venue was changed to ,O
Sentence: 111," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 111,after ,O
Sentence: 111," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 111,denied flight clearance to the ,O
Sentence: 111," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 111,leader 's helicopters ,O
Sentence: 112," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 112,of trying to stop the ,O
Sentence: 112," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 112,meeting by keeping ,O
Sentence: 112," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 112,grounded ,O
Sentence: 113," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 113,and ,O
Sentence: 113," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 113,"officials , on civilian affairs , at the ",O
Sentence: 113," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 113,crossing between ,O
Sentence: 113," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 113,and the ,O
Sentence: 113," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 114," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 114," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 114,said ,O
Sentence: 114," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 114,had decided against flying to the ,O
Sentence: 114," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 114,"on Thursday , after ",O
Sentence: 114," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 114," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 114,and would not be free until Monday ,O
Sentence: 115,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 115," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 115,to meet ,O
Sentence: 115," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 115,in ,O
Sentence: 115," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 115,after flight ban ,O
Sentence: 116,JERUSALEM 1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 116," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 116,will meet ,O
Sentence: 116," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 116,in ,O
Sentence: 116," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 116,on Thursday after ,O
Sentence: 116," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 116,said the right-wing ,O
Sentence: 116," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 116,government had barred the ,O
Sentence: 116," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 116,leader from flying to the ,O
Sentence: 116," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 116,for talks with the former prime minister ,O
Sentence: 117,The meeting between ,O
Sentence: 117," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 117,and ,O
Sentence: 117," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 117,will take place at ,O
Sentence: 117," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 117,checkpoint in ,O
Sentence: 117," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 117,and not in ,O
Sentence: 117," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 117,"as planned , ",O
Sentence: 117," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 118," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 118,government had barred ,O
Sentence: 118," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 118,from overflying ,O
Sentence: 118," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 118,in a ,O
Sentence: 118," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 118,helicopter to the ,O
Sentence: 118," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 118,in an attempt to bar the meeting with ,O
Sentence: 118," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 119," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 119,Prime Minister ,O
Sentence: 119," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 119,has accused opposition leader ,O
Sentence: 119," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 120,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 120," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 120," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 120,embassy says ,O
Sentence: 120," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 120,guards going home ,O
Sentence: 121,Hilary ,O
Sentence: 121," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 121," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 121,1996-08-22 Three ,O
Sentence: 121," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 121,guards brought to the ,O
Sentence: 121," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 121,last week by ,O
Sentence: 121," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 121,hostages who escaped from the ,O
Sentence: 121," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 121,militia will return to ,O
Sentence: 121," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 121,"in a few days , the ",O
Sentence: 121," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 121,embassy in ,O
Sentence: 121," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 121,said on Thursday ,O
Sentence: 122,Our ambassador is in touch with the ,O
Sentence: 122," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 122,foreign ministry ,O
Sentence: 123,Their return to ,O
Sentence: 123," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 125,"There is no objection to their travel , he added ",O
Sentence: 126,The three ,O
Sentence: 126," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 126,guards were overpowered by seven ,O
Sentence: 126," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 126,aircrew who escaped to ,O
Sentence: 126," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 126,state ,O
Sentence: 126," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 126," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 126,militia in ,O
Sentence: 126," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 126,in southern ,O
Sentence: 126," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 127," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 127,said on Monday it would hand over the three to the ,O
Sentence: 127," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 127,", possibly last Tuesday ",O
Sentence: 128,It has since been silent on the issue ,O
Sentence: 129," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 129,or the ,O
Sentence: 129," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 129,capital ,O
Sentence: 129," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 129," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 130," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 130,is the headquarters of the opposition ,O
Sentence: 130," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 130,militia ,O
Sentence: 131,Kabul is controlled by President ,O
Sentence: 131," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 131,"'s government , which ",O
Sentence: 131," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 131,is fighting to overthrow ,O
Sentence: 132," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 133," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 133,did not elaborate ,O
Sentence: 134,The ,O
Sentence: 134," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 134,", working for the ",O
Sentence: 134," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 134,firm in the ,O
Sentence: 134," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 134,republic of ,O
Sentence: 134," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 134,", were taken hostage after a ",O
Sentence: 134," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 135,Taleban said its shipment of ammunition from ,O
Sentence: 135," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 135,was evidence of ,O
Sentence: 135," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 135,military support for ,O
Sentence: 135," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 135,'s government ,O
Sentence: 138," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 138,"cargo plane last Friday , left the ",O
Sentence: 138," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 138,capital ,O
Sentence: 138," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 138,for home on Sunday ,O
Sentence: 139,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 139," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 139,'s ,O
Sentence: 139," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 139,meets ,O
Sentence: 139," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 139,'s ,O
Sentence: 139," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 140," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 140,1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 140," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 140,President ,O
Sentence: 140," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 140,has told visiting ,O
Sentence: 140," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 140,ultra-nationalist ,O
Sentence: 140," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 140,that ,O
Sentence: 140," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 140," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 140,", official ",O
Sentence: 140," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 140,newspapers said on Thursday ,O
Sentence: 141,President ,O
Sentence: 141," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 141,stressed during the meeting ,O
Sentence: 141," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 141," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 141,", the papers said ",O
Sentence: 142,They said ,O
Sentence: 142," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 142,told ,O
Sentence: 142," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 142,before he left ,O
Sentence: 142," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 142,on Wednesday that his ,O
Sentence: 142," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 142,and the ,O
Sentence: 142," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 142," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 142," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 142,after its 1990 invasion of ,O
Sentence: 142," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 143," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 143,said on Tuesday he would press the ,O
Sentence: 143," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 143,government to help end ,O
Sentence: 143," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 143,trade sanctions on ,O
Sentence: 143," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 143,and blamed ,O
Sentence: 143," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 143,for delaying establishment of good ties with ,O
Sentence: 143," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 144," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 144,"stand is firm , namely we are calling on ( the ",O
Sentence: 144," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 144,) government to end the economic embargo on ,O
Sentence: 144," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 144,and resume trade ties between ,O
Sentence: 144," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 144,and ,O
Sentence: 144," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 144,", he told reporters ",O
Sentence: 145,Zhirinovsky visited ,O
Sentence: 145," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 145,twice in 1995 ,O
Sentence: 146," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 146,"'s presidency , which extended ",O
Sentence: 146," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 146,'s term for seven more years ,O
Sentence: 147,-DOCSTART- PRESS DIGEST - ,O
Sentence: 147," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 147,- Aug 22 ,O
Sentence: 150,THAWRA - ,O
Sentence: 150," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 150,'s President ,O
Sentence: 150," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 150,meets with chairman of the ,O
Sentence: 150," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 150,liberal democratic party ,O
Sentence: 150," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 151," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 151," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 151,foreign minister says ,O
Sentence: 151," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 151,will take part in the ,O
Sentence: 151," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 151,trade fair that will be held in November ,O
Sentence: 152," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 152,port in the ,O
Sentence: 152," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 153," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 153,PRESS DIGEST - ,O
Sentence: 153," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 153,- Aug 22 ,O
Sentence: 156," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 156,and the government ,O
Sentence: 157,- Prime Minister ,O
Sentence: 157," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 157,: ,O
Sentence: 157," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 157,threats do no serve peace ,O
Sentence: 158,AS-SAFIR - Parliament Speaker ,O
Sentence: 158," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 158,: ,O
Sentence: 158," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 158,is preparing for war against ,O
Sentence: 158," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 158,and ,O
Sentence: 158," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 159," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 159,Parliamentary battle in ,O
Sentence: 159," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 159,.. The three main lists have been prepared ,O
Sentence: 160," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 160,elections last Sunday ,O
Sentence: 161,AD-DIYAR - Financial negotiations between ,O
Sentence: 161," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 161,and ,O
Sentence: 161," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 162," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 162," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 163,NIDA'A ,O
Sentence: 163," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 163,- ,O
Sentence: 163," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 163,Patriarch ,O
Sentence: 163," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 164,-DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 164," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 164,live and feeder cattle calls range mixed ,O
Sentence: 165,CHICAGO 1996-08-22 Early calls on ,O
Sentence: 165," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 170,-DOCSTART- Kindercare says debt buy to hit Q1 results ,O
Sentence: 171,"MONTGOMERY , ",O
Sentence: 171," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 172," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 172," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 174,The notes were bought for $ 31.5 million ,O
Sentence: 175,Philip ,O
Sentence: 175," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 176,-DOCSTART- RESEARCH ALERT - ,O
Sentence: 176," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 176,starts ,O
Sentence: 176," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 177," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 177,analyst ,O
Sentence: 177," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 177,started ,O
Sentence: 177," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 177,"with an outperform rating , his office said ",O
Sentence: 180,-- ,O
Sentence: 180," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 180,closed at 38-1/2 Wednesday ,O
Sentence: 181,-- ,O
Sentence: 181," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 181,", ",O
Sentence: 181," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 181,", 212-859-1736 -DOCSTART- ",O
Sentence: 181," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 181,Q2 net rises ,O
Sentence: 182,PHOENIX 1996-08-22 Summary of ,O
Sentence: 182," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 182," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 182,socialists give PM green light for election ,O
Sentence: 183,ATHENS 1996-08-22 The ,O
Sentence: 183," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 183," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 183,told reporters on Thursday ,O
Sentence: 184,Prime Minister ,O
Sentence: 184," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 184," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 185," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 185,", ",O
Sentence: 185," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 185,+301 3311812-4 -DOCSTART- PRESS DIGEST - ,O
Sentence: 185," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 185,- ,O
Sentence: 185," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 185,Aug 22 ,O
Sentence: 186," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 186,", dated Aug 23 ",O
Sentence: 187,FRONT PAGE -- ,O
Sentence: 187," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 189,BUSINESS PAGES -- Shutdown of ,O
Sentence: 189," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 189,'s ,O
Sentence: 189," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 189,"factories points up shoe industry crisis , with ",O
Sentence: 189," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 190,-- Secretary general of the ,O
Sentence: 190," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 190,trade union at ,O
Sentence: 190," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 191,-- ,O
Sentence: 191," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 191,+33 1 42 21 53 81 -DOCSTART- Well repairs to lift ,O
Sentence: 191," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 191,oil output - ,O
Sentence: 191," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 192," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 192,1996-08-22 Three plugged water injection wells on the ,O
Sentence: 192," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 192,oilfield off ,O
Sentence: 192," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 192,"will be reopened over the next month , operator ",O
Sentence: 192," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 192,( ,O
Sentence: 192," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 192,) said on Thursday ,O
Sentence: 193," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 193,"output to roughly 220,000 bpd , according to the company 's ",O
Sentence: 193," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 193,newsletter ,O
Sentence: 195,-- ,O
Sentence: 195," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 195,newsroom +47 22 42 50 41 -DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 195," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 195,April trade surplus 3.8 billion markka - ,O
Sentence: 195," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 196," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 196,1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 196," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 196," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 196,( ,O
Sentence: 196," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 196,) said in a statement on Thursday ,O
Sentence: 200," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 200,joined the ,O
Sentence: 200," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 200,at the start of 1995 ,O
Sentence: 201,-- ,O
Sentence: 201," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 201,+358 - 0 - 680 50 245 -DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 201," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 201,state raises tap sale price to 99.95 ,O
Sentence: 202,AMSTERDAM 1996-08-22 The ,O
Sentence: 202," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 202,raised the price for tap sales of the ,O
Sentence: 202," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 203," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 203,to 15.00 ,O
Sentence: 203," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 203,until further notice ,O
Sentence: 205,-- ,O
Sentence: 205," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 205,newsroom +31 20 504 5000 -DOCSTART- ,O
Sentence: 205," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 205,farm ministry tells consumers to avoid ,O
Sentence: 205," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 205,mutton ,O
Sentence: 206,BONN 1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 206," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 206,'s ,O
Sentence: 206," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 207,Until this is cleared up by the ,O
Sentence: 207," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 207," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 207,told ,O
Sentence: 207," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 207,television ,O
Sentence: 212," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 212,and ,O
Sentence: 212," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 212,that under laboratory conditions sheep could contract ,O
Sentence: 212," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 212,( ,O
Sentence: 212," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 212,) -- mad cow disease ,O
Sentence: 213,But some members of the ,O
Sentence: 213," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 217,ZDF said ,O
Sentence: 217," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 217,"imported 47,600 sheep from ",O
Sentence: 217," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 217,"last year , nearly half of total imports ",O
Sentence: 218,"It brought in 4,275 tonnes of ",O
Sentence: 218," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 218,"mutton , some 10 percent of overall imports ",O
Sentence: 219,After the ,O
Sentence: 219," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 219," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 219,imposed a worldwide ban on ,O
Sentence: 219," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 219,beef exports ,O
Sentence: 221,-DOCSTART- GOLF - SCORES AT ,O
Sentence: 221," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 222," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,1996-08-22 Scores from the $ 2.1 million ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 222,"after the first round Thursday at the 7,149 yard , par 70 ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,course ( players ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,unless stated ) : 66 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,) 68 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,69 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,70 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,) 71 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,72 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,73 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,74 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,) 75 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,", ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,) 76 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,77 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,") , ",O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,79 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,81 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 222,( ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 222,) -DOCSTART- SOCCER - ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 222,BEAT 2-1 ,O
Sentence: 222," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 223," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 223,1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 223," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 223,( ,O
Sentence: 223," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 223,) beat 2-1 ( halftime 1-1 ) ,O
Sentence: 223," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 223,( ,O
Sentence: 223," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 223,) in their ,O
Sentence: 223," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 224,Scorers : ,O
Sentence: 224," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 224,- ,O
Sentence: 224," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 224,"( 32nd ) , ",O
Sentence: 224," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 224,( 84th ) ,O
Sentence: 224," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 224,- ,O
Sentence: 224," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 224,"( 24th ) Attendance : 8,000 ",O
Sentence: 224," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 224," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 225," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 225,-DOCSTART- HORSE RACING - ,O
Sentence: 225," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 225,ENDS 25-YEAR WAIT FOR TRAINER ,O
Sentence: 225," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 226," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 226,", ",O
Sentence: 226," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 226,1996-08-22 Sir ,O
Sentence: 226," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 226," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 226,", a 100-30 chance , won the ",O
Sentence: 226," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 226,on Thursday ,O
Sentence: 227," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 227,"( 16-1 ) , trained by ",O
Sentence: 227," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 227,and ridden by ,O
Sentence: 227," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 228," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 228,"( 11-4 ) , last year 's ",O
Sentence: 228," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 228,winner at ,O
Sentence: 228," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 228," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 228,in fourth ,O
Sentence: 229,"Pivotal , a ",O
Sentence: 229," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 229,"winner in June , may now be aimed at this season 's ",O
Sentence: 229," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 229,", ",O
Sentence: 229," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 229,'s top sprint race ,O
Sentence: 231,He added : It 's very sad to beat ,O
Sentence: 231," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 231,because I am godfather to his daughter ,O
Sentence: 232,Like ,O
Sentence: 232," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 232,", ",O
Sentence: 232," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 232,", trainer of ",O
Sentence: 232," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 235,-DOCSTART- HORSE RACING - NUNTHORPE STAKES RESULTS ,O
Sentence: 236,"YORK , ",O
Sentence: 236," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 236,1996-08-22 Result of the ,O
Sentence: 236," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 236," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 236,100-30 ( ridden by ,O
Sentence: 236," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 236,) 2. ,O
Sentence: 236," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 236,16-1 ( ,O
Sentence: 236," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 236,) 3. ,O
Sentence: 236," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 236,11-4 ( ,O
Sentence: 236," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 236,) Eight ran ,O
Sentence: 237,Favourite : ,O
Sentence: 237," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 237,"( 7-4 ) finished 4th Distances : a short head , 1-1/4 lengths ",O
Sentence: 238,Winner owned by the ,O
Sentence: 238," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 238,and trained by Sir ,O
Sentence: 238," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 238,at ,O
Sentence: 238," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 239," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 239," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 240," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 240,", ",O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,"1996-08-21 Results from the $ 450,000 ",O
Sentence: 240," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 240," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 240,( ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,) beat ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 240,( ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,) 1-6 6-4 6-3 4 - ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 240,( ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,) beat ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 240,( ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,) 6-2 7-5 ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 240,( ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,) beat 7 - ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 240,( ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,) 6-3 4-6 6-4 8 - ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 240,( ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,) beat ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 240,( ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 240,) 6-4 6-2 -DOCSTART- TENNIS - RESULTS AT ,O
Sentence: 240," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 241," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 241,", ",O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,1996-08-21 Results from the ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,( ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,) beat ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,( ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,) 6-3 6-2 ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,( ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,) beat 3 - ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,( ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,) 3-6 6-4 6-3 ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,( ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,) beat 6 - ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,( ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,) 5-7 6-3 3-0 retired ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,( ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,) beat ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,( ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 241,) 7-6 ( 7-4 ) 7-5 -DOCSTART- SOCCER - ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 241,SAD OVER ,O
Sentence: 241," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 241,PARTING ,O
Sentence: 242,LONDON 1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 242," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 242," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 242,", the club he led to the ",O
Sentence: 242," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 242,premier league title in 1994-95 ,O
Sentence: 243," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 243,had parted by mutual consent ,O
Sentence: 250,-DOCSTART- CRICKET - ,O
Sentence: 250," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 250,SCORES ,O
Sentence: 251,LONDON 1996-08-22 Close of play scores in four-day ,O
Sentence: 251," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 251,cricket matches on Thursday : Second day At ,O
Sentence: 251," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 251,: ,O
Sentence: 251," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 251,326 ( ,O
Sentence: 251," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 251,"95 not out , ",O
Sentence: 251," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 251,69 ; ,O
Sentence: 251," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 251,7-73 ) ,O
Sentence: 252,Somerset 236-4 ( ,O
Sentence: 252," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 252,85 ) ,O
Sentence: 253,Firsy day At ,O
Sentence: 253," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 253,: ,O
Sentence: 253," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 253,280 ( ,O
Sentence: 253," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 253,"63 , ",O
Sentence: 253," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 253,52 ; ,O
Sentence: 253," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 253,5-68 ) ,O
Sentence: 254,Essex 72-0 ,O
Sentence: 255,At ,O
Sentence: 255," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 255,: ,O
Sentence: 255," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 255,128-1 ( ,O
Sentence: 255," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 255,"59 , ",O
Sentence: 255," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 255,53 not out ) v ,O
Sentence: 255," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 256," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 256," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 256,: ,O
Sentence: 256," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 256,343-8 ( ,O
Sentence: 256," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 256,"108 , ",O
Sentence: 256," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 256,67 not out ) v ,O
Sentence: 256," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 257," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 257," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 257,: ,O
Sentence: 257," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 257,368-7 ( ,O
Sentence: 257," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 257,"145 , ",O
Sentence: 257," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 257,"59 not out , ",O
Sentence: 257," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 257,51 ) v ,O
Sentence: 257," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 258," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 258," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 258,: ,O
Sentence: 258," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 258,392-6 ( ,O
Sentence: 258," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 258,"143 not out , ",O
Sentence: 258," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 258,107 ) v ,O
Sentence: 258," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 259," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 259," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 259,: ,O
Sentence: 259," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 259,255-9 ( ,O
Sentence: 259," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 259,"57 not out , ",O
Sentence: 259," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 259,52 ) v ,O
Sentence: 259," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 260," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 260," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 260,: ,O
Sentence: 260," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 260,305-5 ( ,O
Sentence: 260," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 260,"66 not out , ",O
Sentence: 260," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 260,"66 , ",O
Sentence: 260," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 260,57 ) v ,O
Sentence: 260," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 261," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 261,CRICKET - ,O
Sentence: 261," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 261,V ,O
Sentence: 261," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 261,FINAL TEST SCOREBOARD ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 262,and ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 262,at ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 262,on Thursday : ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 262,first innings ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,b ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,31 ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,b ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,44 ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,c ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,b ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,12 ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,lbw b ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,54 ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,not out 94 ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,b ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,17 ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,b ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,5 ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,Bowling ( to date ) : ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,"25-8-61-1 , ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,"20-6-70-2 , ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,"12-1-41-1 , ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,"27-5-78-2 , ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,6-1-17-0 ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 262,: ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,", ",O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,-DOCSTART- SOCCER - ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 262,BACK IN ,O
Sentence: 262," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 262,SQUAD AFTER 20 MONTHS ,O
Sentence: 263,GLASGOW 1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 263," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 263,'s ,O
Sentence: 263," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 263,", who scored twice against ",O
Sentence: 263," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 263,"on Wednesday , was picked on Thursday for the ",O
Sentence: 263," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 263,squad after a 20-month exile ,O
Sentence: 264,Glasgow ,O
Sentence: 264," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 264,striker ,O
Sentence: 264," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 264," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 264,qualifier against ,O
Sentence: 264," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 264,in ,O
Sentence: 264," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 265," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 265," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 265,caps in December 1994 ,O
Sentence: 266,Scotland manager ,O
Sentence: 266," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 266,said on Thursday : I 've watched ,O
Sentence: 266," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 267,Ally ,O
Sentence: 267," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 267,is also in great scoring form at the moment ,O
Sentence: 268,Celtic 's ,O
Sentence: 268," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 269,-DOCSTART- CRICKET - ,O
Sentence: 269," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 269,100-2 AT LUNCH ON FIRST DAY OF THIRD TEST ,O
Sentence: 270,LONDON 1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 270," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 270," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 270,at ,O
Sentence: 270," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 270,on Thursday ,O
Sentence: 271,-DOCSTART- SOCCER - ,O
Sentence: 271," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 271,SIGNS FOUR-YEAR CONTRACT WITH ,O
Sentence: 271," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 272," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 272,1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 272," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 272,midfielder ,O
Sentence: 272," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 272,has signed a new four-year contract with ,O
Sentence: 272," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 272,league and ,O
Sentence: 272," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 272,champions ,O
Sentence: 272," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 273," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 273," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 273,"and we are delighted , said ",O
Sentence: 273," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 273,manager ,O
Sentence: 273," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 273,on Thursday ,O
Sentence: 274,-DOCSTART- TENNIS - RESULTS AT ,O
Sentence: 274," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 275," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 275,1996-08-21 Results from the ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat 1 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-3 7-5 ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat 2 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-7 ( 3-7 ) 6-4 6-4 3 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 7-5 6-3 4 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-3 6-2 6 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-4 6-2 7 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 7-6 ( 7-3 ) 6-3 ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat 8 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-3 3-6 7-6 ( 8-6 ) 9 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 7-6 ( 7-1 ) 6-4 ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat 11 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-1 6-2 ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat 12 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-3 6-4 ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat 13 - ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 5-7 7-6 ( 7-1 ) 7-6 ( 13-11 ) ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-3 1-6 6-3 ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 7-6 ( 7-2 ) 6-2 ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) 6-3 4-6 6-1 ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,) beat ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,( ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 275,") , walkover -DOCSTART- CRICKET - ",O
Sentence: 275," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 275,SIGNS FOR ,O
Sentence: 275," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 276," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 276," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 276,1996-08-22 ,O
Sentence: 276," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 276,provincial side ,O
Sentence: 276," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 276,said on Thursday they had signed ,O
Sentence: 276," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 276,fast bowler ,O
Sentence: 276," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 276,on a one year contract ,O
Sentence: 277,"Millns , who toured ",O
Sentence: 277," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 277,with ,O
Sentence: 277," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 277,"A in 1992/93 , replaces former ",O
Sentence: 277," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 277,all-rounder ,O
Sentence: 277," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 277,as ,O
Sentence: 277," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 277,'s overseas professional ,O
Sentence: 278,-DOCSTART- SOCCER - ,O
Sentence: 278," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 278,RESULTS ,O
Sentence: 279,TIRANA 1996-08-22 Results of ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <MISC> "" Var_MISC "" </MISC> """,MISC
Sentence: 279," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 279,: ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 279,( ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 279,) 0 ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 279,( ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 279,) 2 ( halftime 0-0 ) Scorers : ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 279,"( 50th minute ) , ",O
Sentence: 279," "" <PER> "" Var_PER "" </PER> """,PER
Sentence: 279,"( 54th ) Attendance : 5,000 ",O
Sentence: 279," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 279,win 3-0 on aggregate In ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 279,: ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <ORG> "" Var_ORG "" </ORG> """,ORG
Sentence: 279,( ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 279,) 2 ,O
Sentence: 279," "" <LOC> "" Var_LOC "" </LOC> """,LOC
Sentence: 279,( ,O
